Angel Gabriel Salvador Castañeda

Software engineer



PHONE 3334945117

LINKS Github, Linkedin

EMAIL 02angelsalvador@gmail.com

Profile

I made things for the web since 2016. Hi, I'm Angel, in the company I currently work for, I'm learning new things continually because I am developing complete applications from scratch and maintaining old systems, using React JS, Php, and Docker SQI server. Most of the time, solving problems isn't a problem for me because I like to solve the issues and learn from them.

Skills

HTML5 & CSS3

React js

Docker

JavaScript

PHP

jQuery

Mysql

Ant design

SQL Server

Git

Employment History

May 2023 – At present

HOME OFFICE

Full stack developer

Asipona Manzanillo

In this company I learned a lot about software development, I am developing complete systems, from backend, frontend, and DB by myself, using the technologies of PHP, SQL server, react, antd, vite, docker, rest API

Jan 2020 - May 2023

HOME OFFICE

Front-end and Back-end developer

IBM

On this company, I worked with PHP, Mysql for the backend development. Dojo Js, React js for the front end

Feb 2017 - Aug 2019

Front-end and Back-end developer

LIMA, COL. Dirección de Sistemas - Universidad de Colima

In this university department, I worked with technology like Php, Javascript, SQL, Mysql for database, Css3, Html5, Javascript vanilla and Jquery for Front-end and Git for version control.

Sep 2018 - Sep 2019

COLIMA, COL.

Front-end developer

Coddy (www.coddy.com.mx)

In this company, I had a part-time job and I worked with technology like vanilla js, Vue js, HTML5, CSS3 and Jquery in some projects and Git for version control.

Education

COLIMA, COL.

Aug 2016 – June 2020

University of Colima

Software engineer

Languages

English TOEFL Exam Score: 430 Spanish Native Language